And as you see it says want to see more join learners community and create a free account.
So that's exactly what I'm going to be doing at the beginning, you know, I want to sign
in in order to be able to use the tool with the full capacity of its free planning, right?
So I can click on create free account or I can click on sign in.
So I try signing in to see if it's possible to do that with my Google account.
So I click sign in.
It says failed to fetch.
Yes.
So now as you see it says sign up or login with Canva Apple Google Microsoft.
So I click on Google and I wait.
And as you see it says choose an account to continue to learn on the AI.
So I choose this account of mine, right?
I click it and I wait.
And as you see, it says signing to learnerdo.ai Google will allow learner to access this information
about you.
So again, I click continue and wait.
And as you see, after we have signed in, we'll be forwarded to the page app.learnerdo.ai.